Stewie,  what's  the
full  form  of
USB?
Ah,  Peter,  it's
universal  serial  bus,
of  course.
Universal  serial  bus,
that's  a  mouthful.
Yes,  Peter,  it's
a  standard  interface
for  connecting  devices
to  a  computer.
I  see,  so
it's  like  a
special  highway  for
data?
Exactly,  Peter.
And  USB  has
evolved  over  the
years
to  support  faster
speeds  and  more
devices.
Wow,  I  had
no  idea  it
was  so  complex.
Well,  Peter,  it's
actually  quite  simple
once  you  understand
it.
Okay,  so  what
about  USB -A,
USB -B,  and
USB -C?
Ah,  Peter,  those
are  just  different
types  of  USB
connectors.
Types  of  connectors?
I  thought  they
were  different  versions.
No,  Peter,  they're
just  different  shapes
and  sizes.
I  get  it
now,  thanks  Stewie.
Any  time,  Peter.